# Rogelio Schevenin Jr

# Computer Science Undergraduate

An HSF Scholar who is a self-motivated Desktop Software Engineer and Web Developer with mid level of experience working on multiple projects. Published on the App Store and have built website portfolios for myself, for friends, family, and clients. Passionate and hardworking with penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in role with company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects with a primary focus in providing a real world impact through an internship or job as a Software Engineer.

## **Work History**

## 2016-02 -Current

## Web Developer

PHS Boys Soccer Booster Club, Woodland, CA

- Developed and currently maintain e-commerce site to maximize company revenue and support ~500 unique monthly visitors.
- Determined coding requirements for site creation, including e-commerce capability and specialized scripts via PayPal integration.
- Strengthened company brand and identity by creating distinctive website and logo.

## 2019-06 -2019-08

## **Activity Leader II**

City Of Woodland, Woodland, CA

- Ensured group of 60 kids participating in city Youth Summer Camp (STFC) were safe and enjoyed summer.
- Responsible for working with team of like-minded leaders to plan activities, leading youth through activities, and keeping parents updated with following week's activity schedule.
- Occasionally responsible for communicating with kids and their parents to resolve issues.
- Fostered environment where youth were able to developed personal relationships.
- Maintained excellent attendance record, with 100%

## Contact

#### **Address**

2501 Ortiz Avenue Woodland, CA, 95776

#### **Phone**

530-383-1476

#### E-mail

rogelio@schevenin.com

### **Skills**

Software Development (Java, Python, Swift)



Development standards



HTML and CSS proficiency



Algorithms and data structures



Troubleshooting



attendance rate.

## 2018-07 -2019-08

#### Sales Associate

Davis Legacy Soccer League, Davis, CA

- Worked with other Sales Associates to collaboratively reach targets, consistently meeting or exceeding personal quotas.
- Increased revenue by selling tickets to over 5000 customers.

## 2018-06 -2018-08

## **Activity Leader I**

City Of Woodland, Woodland, CA

- Ensured kids participating in city Youth Summer
  Camp (STFC) had safe and enjoyable summer.
- Responsible for working with team of like-minded leaders to plan activities and lead youth through activities.
- Maintained excellent attendance record, with 100% attendance rate.

## **Education**

## 2019-08 -Current

# **Bachelor of Science: Computer Science**

San Diego State University - San Diego, CA

- Member of Weber Honors College
- Minor in Interdisciplinary Studies
- Coursework in Algorithm Design and Data Structures
- 3.54/4.00 GPA